http://www.dalesjetsports.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your right to privacy is very important. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. We believe this information should only be used to help us provide you with better service.
Below is a summary of Dale’s Jet Sports online privacy policy
What personal information do we collect?
In general, when you visit our websites and access information you remain anonymous. If you utilize various forms on our site, certain information is requested from you. We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission.
There are occasions where we will ask for additional information. We do this to be able to better understand your needs, and provide you with services that we believe may be valuable to you. Some examples of information our website collects are name, address and phone number. We give you the opportunity to elect not to receive materials from us. If you sign up a mailing or e-mail list, the information collected from you will determine what gets sent to you. We hate to receive unwanted junk mail just as much as you.
Protecting your privacy:
We will take appropriate steps to protect your privacy. We will also take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information in storage. For example, if you supply us with your credit card information to make an online purchase, this information is not stored in a database or computer accessible from the Internet. Additionally, access to personally identifiable information is limited to Dale’s Jet Sports employees needing such access to perform their job function.
We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. However, we may need to provide your name and delivery address to third parties that Dale’s Jet Sports uses for the purposes of delivering specific services to you (e.g., third party supply houses, or a shipping company if you have asked us to send something to you). Likewise, we will share your credit card information with the appropriate authorization and processing companies, in the event you were to purchase something via credit card. These companies will not use this information for any other purpose and will not disclose the information to anyone else.
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these third party sites.
Children’s privacy:
We strive to keep our website directed to a general audience. Some areas of our site may be objectionable to some younger viewers. We believe that governing what a child sees on the Internet is the responsibility of the parents. However, Dale’s Jet Sports will do what it can to protect young children from questionable material. Also, if we know a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will either obtain parental permission or delete the information.
Use of cookies:
Dale’s Jet Sports website may use cookies for various reasons. Cookies enable us to provide you with a better experience by allowing us to understand what areas of the website are of interest to our visitors. Dale’s Jet Sports can only read cookies from our website. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our website.
Data storage and processing in the United States:
The portions of our website that collects information will process and store that information in databases located in the United States.
How can you update the personal information you have provided to Dale’s Jet Sports?
You can help Dale’s Jet Sports maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying Dale’s Jet Sports of any changes to your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. By sending current information to info @ dalesjetsports.com or by resubmitting the information via the appropriate form, we can keep our records current.
If you need assistance in updating your information, please contact Customer Support at info@dalesjetspors.com. To aid in processing your request, please include your contact information (name, address, e-mail), the name of the Dale’s Jet Sports program or service you need the changes applied to, and the details of the change (e.g., update email address). This information you provide to Dale’s Jet Sports Customer Support will also be covered by this policy.
We welcome your questions or concerns about this policy.
Please eMail Dale’s Jet Sports with questions or concerns
